<search function="yn">
  <name>Yubnub</name>
  <category>Search The Web</category>
  <contributor>Ryan Carpenter</contributor>
  <link>http://www.yubnub.org/</link>
  <description>
    Yubnub calls itself a (social) command line for the web.  It is essentially a web-based version of DQSD in which searches are added and edited by all users at once.<br/>
    Making Yubnub your default DQSD search (by adding "defaultsearch='yn';" to <a href="view-source:file:///C:/Program%20Files/Quick%20Search%20Deskbar/localprefs.js">localprefs.js</a>) will still direct your searches to Google, but give you access to the expanded set of searches on Yubnub.<br/>
    <div class="helpboxDescLabels">Switches:</div>
    <table class="helpboxDescTable">
      <tr><td>ls</td><td> - </td><td>(list) Show all of the searches availible on Yubnub</td></tr>
      <tr><td>ge</td><td> - </td><td>(golden eggs) Show the most useful searches on Yubnub</td></tr>
      <tr><td>man</td><td> - </td><td>Display help for a Yubnub command</td></tr>
      <tr><td>less</td><td> - </td><td>Like the less command for GNU/Linux and other *nix variants. Shows the straight source code for any file on the Internet.</td></tr>
      <tr><td>vil</td><td> - </td><td>Search McAfee's Virus Info Library for a virus, worm or hoax.</td></tr>
      <tr><td>trailer</td><td> - </td><td>Uses Google to search Apple for the most likely movie trailer.</td></tr>
      <tr><td>fanfree</td><td> - </td><td>Returns printer-friendly movie listings from Fandango (without advertisements). Takes city and state or zip code as a parameter.</td></tr>
      <tr><td>nearby</td><td> - </td><td>Coordinate Conversion and Location Links. Enter a coordinate (eg GB/Irish Grid Reference, UK Postcode, US Zip, Lat/Long, UTM, NAC Universal Address) and it will be converted to other formats, as well as providing links to a Wide range of sites based on that location.</td></tr>
      <tr><td>psize</td><td> - </td><td>Page size checker for the given url. Gives a list of the sizes of the found linked elements. Smart enough to detect page compression and when it does will show compresssed and uncompressed sizes (real, not estimated).</td></tr>
      <tr><td>sc</td><td> - </td><td>Shoutcast search engine call</td></tr>
    </table>
    Yubnub switches do not require a / character, they only need to be the first word entered.
    <div class="helpboxDescLabels">Examples:</div>
    <table class="helpboxDescTable">
      <tr><td>yn ls</td></tr>
      <tr><td>yn tts All your base are belong to us</td></tr>
      <tr><td>yn flk sunset</td></tr>
      <tr><td>yn man flk</td></tr>
      <tr><td>yn newbooks</td></tr>
    </table>
  </description>
  <form name="ynf"
        method="post"
        action="http://yubnub.org/parser/parse">
    <input type="hidden" name="command" value="" />
  </form>
  <script><![CDATA[
    function yn(q)
    {
      if( nullArgs("yn", q) )
        return false;

      vars = q.split(" ")
      if (vars.length == 2)
      {
        document.ynf.command.value = q;
        submitForm(ynf);
      }
      else
        nullArgs("yn","?");
    }
  ]]></script>
  <copyright>
    The following applies if this file is included and distributed with Dave's Quick Search Deskbar:
    Copyright (c) 2002 David Bau; Distributed under the terms of the GNU Public License, Version 2 (http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/gpl.txt)
  </copyright>
</search>

